

Aurrel Kondi

Frontend Developer

WORK EXPERIENCE



Intern Frontend Developer, Nepomuk Software

November 2022 - Present

- Experience with modern front-end tools
- Experience with RESTful APIs
- Experience with code versioning tools (such as Git)

Fullstack Web Development Institution: Digital Career Institute GmbH (DCI), Berlin

November 2021- November 2022

- Create UI for various screen sizes and use cases using HTML&CSS.
- Write software using JavaScript React.
- Work with the DOM API to manipulate HTML documents using JavaScript
- Designed, created, and maintained backend applications using Node.js and Express.

Public Relations (PR), Cinco Cavalli Premium Club

February 2014 - May 2018

- Created promotional materials, coordinated with media outlets and social media platforms, and collaborated with other staff to promote events.
- Continuously run customer development and research through surveys, polls, and customer interviews to improve the company communications and product offering.
- Created and scheduled posts for various social media platforms
 Facebook & Instagram

EDUCATION



Bachelor's degree in Economic Informatics Business Management Institution: European University of Tirana

September 2014- July 2017

SUMMARY

A creative web developer with experience in writing simple frontend applications in React and Node.js as a backend connected to a MongoDB database. Strong management skills in social media, marketing, and stakeholders. Highly motivated, detail-oriented, and committed to staying up-to-date with the latest industry trends and best practices.

linkedin.com/in/aurrelkondi

aurrelkondi@hotmail.com +49 176 2016 2083

Berlin, Germany

RELEVANT SKILLS

- Javascript, Vanilla JS, React, Typescript, Tailwind, Bootstrap, HTML5, CSS
- Node.js, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose, Git
- Basic CI/CD (Gitlab CI)

PROJECTS & SOCIAL LINKS

PORTFOLIO

GITHUB

WEATHER APP

TODO LIST

CONVERTER APP

LAZY DEVS